Nott. you bastard!
PEENAK 5
Toh. wait for me. wait!
This way.
Come on. guys. quick!
Hello. bitch? Why are you calling me now?
I'll send you my location.
Okay.
Over here.
Move!
- Damn. how'd it get here?
- He's here. move out.
Shit!
You okay?
First. Balloon. are you alright?
I'll kill everyone you love!
Nott! Nott! Nott!
Get in. everyone!
- Aod!
- That's Aod!
Come on. quick!
Yes. go. go!
First. Balloon. this way. quick!
Damn fancy. I'm in a body wagon.
Aod. what were you thinking?
Aod. step on it!
Let's rest here.
We've come up this high.
Pee Nak can't follow us.
But was that ghost really Nott's brother?
Why was he so vicious?
Right. Did we do something to him?
Why would he want to kill all of us?
Nott. tell us. what did you do?
Why is he hunting us down?
Because you're my friends.
How many more sets left?
Just two or three more and we're done.
Novice. walk mindfully.
Sorry. sir. I'm sorry.
Novice Hunglay. where
are you rushing off to?
Oh. someone's here to see you. Nott.
in front of the chapel.
Yes. thank you. novice.
Yes.
Who is it. novice?
I don't know. sir.
He's got a mean look.
Are you here to see me?
Did you forget me. little brother?
Nin.
I went to your old temple.
The head monk said you left and moved here.
Yes.
You came to see me... what's wrong?
Do I need a reason to come see you?
You're the only family I've got.
I've missed you so much.
I really wanted to see you.
And... how's Dad?
He's doing fine.
What's going on at the temple?
It's Poy Sang Long festival in two days.
It's a mass ordination ceremony
for novices and monks.
Nin...
What's wrong?
No. it's nothing.
I'll leave an ordination set here. okay?
Yeah. I'll go shower first.
Don't forget to inform us. alright?
- Hurry up. okay?
- Dad.
- Yes. thank you. Hurry up.
- Get up.
Dad.
- Who did that?
- That's cruel.
Dad.
Dad!
Thank God you're safe.
That poor kid.
He wanted to become a novice for his dad.
Such a pity...
His father never got to
see him in yellow robes.
Why did you do that?
Call the cops on me. if
you suspect me that much.
Someone like me... no matter where I am.
no one trusts me. no one loves me.
Not even my own brother.
You dropped this at the crime scene.
Yeah. I killed that brat's father.
I did it with my own hands.
Satisfied?
Why did you do it?
Why did you kill him?
They loved each other. I didn't like it.
You have to turn yourself in.
No. I won't.
I won't. I'm going to ordain.
With blood on your hands. you can't ordain!
You bastard!
Nott. listen to me.
If I get ordained.
I can become a decent man again.
And if you keep quiet.
no one will ever know.
Don't make my hands
stain with blood again...
...my little brother.
"Thai Life Insurance invites you
to the annual merit event"
"Poy Sang Long Festival
Wat Luang Nakhin. Chiang Mai"
Bastard Nott. you betrayed me!
Nin. no!
- Move. move!
- Hurry up!
Nin. stop! Nin. Turn yourself in!
Nin. I'm begging you. please.
- Stop it!
- You bastard!
- Go. go. hurry!
- Move. get back!
Stay away! Stay away!
After that. no one ever saw Nin again.
Maybe he's dead.
That ghost looks exactly like him.
Nott. you shouldn't have
reported your brother.
Uh. I... I..
You did the right thing.
He's your brother. but
he's still a murderer.
The guilty should pay for what they did.
How long are we going
to run from this ghost?
Damn! I've had enough!
What is it?
Four down. and we're still standing.
This one's no different.
Exactly.
We're done running.
From prey. we turn into the predators.
- Nott! Nott! Nott!
- Nott! Nott!
Look!
You damn ghost!
Even up here you're still following me?
Get down here!
- Sis!
- Get down here!
- Now!
- Let's go.
- Get down here!
- Forget it. just go!
Go on. we'll go ahead!
Get out of here.
How are you doing?
Doing well. Luang Por.
"Doing well" usually means not...
Novice. manners.
Sorry. Luang Por.
So what brings you here?
I'm here about my brother.
I want to know if anyone found the body
or my brother's remains?
And what makes you sure that Nin is dead?
Because...
his spirit is out there.
killing everyone around me.
If we can bring his body back
for a religious rite.
I think it might finally set his soul free.
We're just lost at this point
but this seems the best start.
from our experience.
Even if it's not working.
Shut it.
Going there is dangerous. you know.
We aren't safe anywhere
not unless we get rid of Pee Nak's ghost.
Can you help us subdue this spirit?
I am a monk. My duty is
to show the way to Dharma.
not to do battle with the supernatural.
Prayers aren't meant to drive away ghosts.
but to free the mind
from fear and delusion.
I'm sore all over.
This path leads to a sacred site
where legends of the occult dwell.
No one dares enter unless they have to.
But do we have to?
Yeah. I guess we do.
Let's go. guys. Ignore this fruity.
Like you're so manly. Balloon.
This is the last lead we have on Nin.
Then let's start right here.
We'll split up and look around.
Anyone finds anything. shout it out. okay?
Hey. First. Let me ask you.
Why'd you split off?
What are you looking for?
Think about it. we're looking for clues.
Clues?
For four parts.
still nothing but this same bullshit.
If you see anything strange.
that's a clue.
Strange equals a clue?
- A clue!
A clue! We got a clue!
On my way. Clue!
- Nott!
- Hold on.
Nott. what is it?
Nott.
Hey!
What. a clue?
What clue? It's blood. you idiot!
You okay. Nott?
Blood!
Every time Nott's like this.
a ghost shows up.
Stop saying stupid crap.
It's broad daylight.
No damn ghost's coming out.
Your mouth is seriously cursed.
I'll kill everyone you love.
Nott
Aod
Mr. Toh!
Balloon. what the hell is that thing?
A dinosaur?
Dino my ass. It's huge and long.
Everyone. come on!
Whoa. ready to go.
Mr.Toh. Watch out!
- Mr.Toh!
Mr.Toh!
Mr.Toh! Careful!
- Run!
- Mr.Toh!
Mr.Toh. hurry! Hurry!
It's coming. Watch out!
Nott!
Everyone. run!
How is everyone?
What was that?
I don't do it anymore.
Didn't you say we'd fight?
Pee Nak showed up.
you bolted like a 400-meter sprint.
That was not running away.
It's called a tactical retreat.
We regroup. then think.
Everyone okay?
Hello. everyone.
You all look like you've been to war.
Not like you were searching for a body.
Novice. maybe you should come with us.
No thanks. I'd feel awkward.
Everyone. besides Pee Nak's ghost.
what was that creature?
Based on the temple legend.
that creature is probably a Makara.
Makara?
There's a legend that
this place was once a battlefield
between the Naga.
protector of Buddhism.
and the Makara. a Himmapan beast.
But the Makara grew jealous that
the Naga was honored
as the symbol of Dharma.
So it sought to defeat him.
The Makara challenged the Naga
to a duel of powers.
The Naga saw that continued fighting
would harm others.
So he said. "If you can swallow me whole.
I'll let you represent
Buddhism instead of me."
The Makara accepted.
It swallowed the Naga whole.
But when it reached the Naga's head.
the Naga grew more heads.
becoming a seven-headed.
The Makara couldn't swallow the heads.
It died with resentment and hatred.
The Naga knew the Makara
couldn't let go of its grudge.
So he used his own blood
to seal the Makara's spirit.
Later. a shrine was built
with the Makara spewing out the Naga.
It symbolizes that the Makara
is like defilements.
love. greed. anger. delusion.
And the Naga is ourselves.
If we cling to attachment and obsession.
- we are like the Naga...
- Focus.
held by the Makara.
unable to escape suffering or let go.
Luang Por. if the Makara was sealed.
why is it out now?
The Makara devours souls.
When a sinner's blood touches the ground.
the seal breaks.
The Makara revives
and devours sinful spirits.
So Nin's blood weakened the seal.
and the Makara is fueling Pee Nak's evil?
Mm.
Well then. evil meets evil. This is fun.
Shh!
What does the Makara's spirit want?
Mr.Toh...
Did you seriously get
food delivery up here?
Uh. I don't think so.
Hi. Mr.Toh!
Hi. Nott!
Peary. sweetheart!
How did you even get here?
Well. didn't you missed me?
Thanks for missing me. Nott.
Wait a second.
First. Balloon...
Aod. just tell them what you want to eat.
Here. basil stir-fry.
you wanted that. right?
Me?
No. you guys.
Wait. why are we at this temple?
Let's go. Bonus. These jerks
tricked me here.
- Sweetie. wait.
- Damn it. I'm going home!
Wait. wait!
Stand still.
Alright. we're sorry for tricking you here.
Please. you've dealt with Pee Nak before.
Help us out.
No way. Bonus. get in the truck.
Same spot.
Stand there.
If you won't help. fine.
But your face is rough like a foot
smeared in makeup.
Crow's feet. forehead lines.
marionette folds.
Why do you look so old? Seriously.
how old are you. 90?
Balloon. you bitch!
Stop.
Not just you. You too!
Gravity's pulling everything down on you.
- Your eyes...
- drooping!
- Your cheeks...
- sagging.
- Your mouth...
- hanging.
And your boobs... so saggy.
They're hanging low. girl.
Sis. is it that bad?
What the hell?
But now you've got a special promo!
You'll receive...
Unlimited free plastic surgery in Korea.
From head...
to toe!
Korea?
- Everything?
- Everything.
- All of it?
- Completely free.
Give me a sec.
Bonus. I think we should
take them up on it.
Let's try it. Okay. deal.
Deal.
Alright.
Okay. deal...
But one condition.
What?
I get to sleep in the same room as Mr.Toh.
Wait. sis.
And Nott too.
Hold on.
Let me check Mr.Toh's schedule.
Surgery?
Her face looks like a war zone.
Would you take that?
Just saying it for now.
Fool them?
- Hey.
- What?
After checking his
schedule. Mr. Toh said...
He's free.
And Nott?
Nott's ready right now.
Alright. deal. You in?
Deal.
Keep it down.
Mr.Toh...
What are they so happy about?
- No. it's you and Mr.Toh.
- Go on in.
I don't know. but it can't be good.
Oh. oh. okay.
Luang Por. please take care of my son Nott.
Whether he ordains or
just sweeps the temple.
Aod.
Yes. Luang Por.
Let this kid stay in your room then.
You can be friends.
Yes. Luang Por. Come on.
I'll take my leave. Luang Por.
What the hell?
I want to ordain here with my brother.
Ordain my ass. You're working with me.
Let's go.
- I'm not going!
- Nin!
Come on. Nin!
I'll ordain with Nott.
You'll abandon me like your mother did?
Come!
- Nin!
- Go!
- Nott! I'm not going!
- Nin!
- Nott!
Come here!
Nin!
Here.
We've known each other since we were kids.
As far as I remember.
we never had dinner together.
How could we?
When I was a novice. you were a temple boy.
When I disrobed. you became a monk.
Here. Cheers!
To our first dinner together.
Our first.
You made this. Aod?
Is it okay?
Yeah. just a bit spicy.
I'll get you some water.
Let me be honest.
I handled the other Pee Naks just fine.
But this one is too much.
Why give up now?
Remember what that...
- Luang Por
- Luang Por...
talked about that crazy long backstory.
I don't even know who's who.
and now they come as a pair.
You're so dumb. You can't remember?
One's Pee Nak. one's Angor.
Makara. you idiot. not Angkor.
I was waiting for it to turn into a tiger.
Keep joking and we'll get eaten.
Damn. this toilet's scary as hell.
Why do you have to pee?
What if I get dragged away?
When you gotta pee. you gotta pee.
Hey. who said I'd sleep
with Mr.Toh and Nott?
Why am I in a room with you guys?
Yeah.
Such a liar.
Talking bad in front of
Buddha. you'll go to hell.
Hello.
Mark my word. You'll never get Toh or Nott.
It's never going to happen.
You will!
I'll arrange it. sweeties.
No more "Mr.Toh."
Call him Toh and Nott.
No matter what you say.
it's never gonna happen.
Just hold on.
You bitch!
It'll happen.
See? Over there.
See?
I told you.
We will.
Listen. sweeties.
Yes?
I'll lock you two in the room.
then let Toh and Nott walk in.
I'll sweetly lock the door.
Then turn off the lights. pitch dark.
You two can... all night
long. no sleep at all.
Get out. hurry. Who could hold that?
Oh shit.
What's that?
Nott!
Nott. what's wrong?
I'm scared. Bonus.
Nott!
Nott. are you okay?
What's wrong?
I can't take it anymore! Fuck!
Peary. keep it down.
You're loud. Bonus. Come here!
Shhh...
Is it quiet enough?
Dead silent. Ahh. a ghost!
Balloon!
Balloon! Help me!
First!
Balloon!
First! First!
First!
Why am I...
- I'm gonna die!
- First!
Help me!
Stop!
Stop hurting my brother.
Nott. help me!
Brother?
Your brother...
Is me!!
Nott!
First!
- How are you. First?
- Nott!
Help me. Peary! Balloon. help!
Balloon's over there!
Easy!
Balloon. easy. he hurts.
Someone tipped off about the culprit
so the headman reported the police.
Do you know who told him?
No.
Why are you asking me?
About Nin...
the culprit.
he's dead.
God blessed! I've waited for this day.
May he rot in hell forever.
Seven generations damned.
Let his whole bloodline fall with him.
I came to ask you to forgive him.
Maybe then he can escape his karma.
Forgive him?
Others can forgive
that bastard if they want.
But I won't.
What are you to that son of a bitch. huh?
Why are you asking for forgiveness for him?
I'm his brother.
- Calm down.
- Do you know what he did to me?
- Let me go. I'll kill him!
- Calm down.
Calm down!
Do you know how evil he was?
Killing people like that?
Let him rot in hell and never find peace.
You too. you piece of shit. Let me go!
Just calm down. Take it easy.
- Let go!
- Sit down.
I'm not calm! Let me go!
Aod. take her out.
Here you go.
Peary and Bonus. I think
you two should leave.
Yeah. this place is more
dangerous than I thought.
Didn't you see last night?
I almost died. girls.
And with baby faces like you two.
Trust me. you're dead meat.
Just saying 'cause I care.
As for that Korea thing.
I'll take you myself.
Stop. Just stop right there.
You think I stay here
because of Korea thing?
- Yeah. Right.
- I'm here for my friends.
because my brothers are in danger.
Exactly. So don't even try to kick us out.
We're not leaving.
Hunglay. please stop eating.
Do you maybe have some sacred stuff
against spirits?
I don't have any... but I know someone
who can help you all.
Who is it. novice?
Ohhh. curious now. aren't you?
Spit it out.
Mae Khee Poo Mia. Shaman Mornthong.
I said let me go!
You want me to let go?
Let me go!
Is this likay or what?
No. Mama.
What are they doing?
Are you scared now?
Go in. novice.
I said let me go!
Get out.
Do it! Do it!
How's that?
This isn't the first time it's come out...
after being sealed away.
And back then who
defeated that Makara. Master?
You are before that person's descendant.
Ewwww!
Can we really trust him?
Seriously. sis. he won't stop eating.
I think he's a scammer.
May I?
Balloon.
Fabulous.
His thingy.
Hey!
Without my permission.
you can't touch anything here.
It'll cling to you.
Is that dancing or what?
Can we really trust this?
Looks scarier than Pee Nak's ghost.
Balloon. what do you think?
Mr. Toh. what exactly are you doubting?
The face? The hair?
The outfit? Or the nails?
All of it.
You're here. huh? Got you!
Hunglay.
Dum!
Master!
Master. stop.
- Master.
- Don't. Nott.
Stop.
- Stop.
- Nott.
- Master. stop!
- No. Nott.
- Master. stop. stop.
- Nott. Nott.
- Shit. stop.
What the hell?
Nott.
Just handle the Makara.
As for Pee Nak. I'll deal with him.
I'll kill them all.
- Master Mornthong.
- Are you okay?
Master Mornthong.
Oh?
Nott.
- Pee Nak.
- Master Mornthong.
Help him.
Nott. Damn it.
Nott.
You hurt my man.
No. no. no. Bonus.
Holy shit!
Hurry. go. Go. Go.
Watch out.
Peary.
Come on. Peary.
You waiting for it to eat you? Come!
Hurry up.
You brainless idiot.
Attention seeker.
Who are you calling that?
Selfish! Bitch.
You bitch. let me!
Balloon.
What the hell's wrong with you? Bitch!
Whoa!
Watch out!
Peary. calm down. Peary!
Don't. Peary.
No! Not my face. Peary!
Shit.
Blood. Blood.
It's my blood. you psycho. Get up.
Damn. everything hurts.
Peary. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Peary. I'm outta here!
Watch out.
Peary. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Peary.
Watch out!
What?
Bitch!
Peary. Peary.
What did I just shove in my mouth?
My foot. that's what!
My mouth hurts. damn it.
Mr. Toh
My mouth hurts.
Serves you right. bitch!
Blood. Is that blood on my face?
Is it from my face?
Blood! Blood!
My blood.
Stop.
Stop. stop. stop. I'm damn tired.
I can't take it.
What the hell?
Bonus!
You really love him. don't you?
Good.
Then I'll make you see
what it's like to lose the one you love.
Nin. no.
Nin. Nin.
- No!
Bonus
Bonus. Bonus
No. no. no. Bonus. no!
Aod?
No. No. Bonus. don't die.
Wake up. Bonus. Wake up. Bonus.
Bonus...
Wake up. Wake up now.
I love you. Bonus.
She rests in peace now.
You have us here.
Bonus
Nin's here.
You've got a toy. Nin?
Got a toy. right?
You that possessive?
- What the hell?
- Not playing with me?
Asshole!
Let me go. assholes!
- Grab him.
- Let me go. assholes!
You hit me over this?
Hit me? You hit me? Take this!
Nott...
Help...
Me...
I bow to ask for blessings.
May my accumulated merit protect Nott
and his friends
keeping them safe and sound
from the wrath of Pee Nak's spirit.
Here. Peary.
Bonus...
I'll avenge you.
Then we'll go home.
Nott's cold-hearted. huh?
He caused this.
yet won't even pick up Bonus' ashes.
Nott isn't like that.
If not. then where is he?
Where's he?
Haven't seen him since morning.
Come out. Nin!
Come out. I'm here.
Come kill me! Kill me now!
You won't get to have fun anymore.
Nott. what are you doing? Let go.
Let go.
Don't do something stupid. Nott.
Don't interfere. This is a family matter!
Stay out of it!
Nott!
So this is the guy Bonus liked?
If your death could bring my sister back.
then just die!
- You want to die. right?
- Enough.
That's enough. Peary.
Nott. am I a stranger to you?
And everyone who came to help you?
Don't you see us as family?
Nott...
I'm really hurt
that you look down on our love for you.
You're a friend and a brother to all of us.
I know we're not bound by blood
but after everything we've been through.
I feel we're closer than real siblings.
But everyone got hurt because of me.
Now Bonus is dead.
It's because of me. It's all because of me.
Everything is my fault.
I don't want to lose anyone else.
See that. Yim?
You blamed him. feel guilty yet?
- Yeah. I get it.
- We don't want to lose you either.
Who could've known he'd go this far?
I'm sorry. everyone. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
We'll get through this.
I...
Let's start over. Nott.
We'll fight together.
Peary. you sure this place
has something to beat that Makara?
Yeah. The ancestor once defeated it.
I've been confused. what
are we looking for here?
Clues. Mama.
Clues again. bitch.
That shaman guarded his stuff like crazy.
If we mess with his things.
won't he get mad?
The shaman's dead. why be scared?
Cause he's dead. that's why I'm scared.
Right! Then go back.
No! Since we're here. just go for it.
Me and First will go together.
Then you go to that risky spot alone.
Oh. why do I go there alone?
Duh. you idiot.
You go there. if something happens.
You just scream. so we both stay safe.
So if I see ghosts. I lead them out.
Then you come out. right?
Slay! You care for me.
you're the best. Balloon!
No biggie. you go that way.
- I will go this way.
- Yeah. yeah.
Go. split.
You're so great. such a "true" friend.
And where do I go?
Come here...
come.
You ass!
Sorry.
You liar bitch.
Oh. fancy tricks.
Balloon!
Pervert shaman!
You pervert. let me go!
Balloon!
Peary!
Let go. let me go!
Peary. First. the danger is right here!
What the hell was that?
I give up.
It's in the chest. bitch.
My arm!
First!
Peary. danger is here.
What is this?
Are you alright?
Surprise!
Damn it. what is that? It sucks your hand.
Let go of my hand.
Here.
First!
It hurts.
Balloon
First
- Peary
- Balloon
First. Balloon. what should I do?
Deal with it for now.
First. First.
First.
First. open your eyes. First.
First. First.
Go. get out of here now. fast.
Go. go.
Hey.
So damn ugly!
Go grab him. stay behind. grab his back.
I'll pull the head off. hurry.
- Will I lose my hand?
- Stay over there.
Pull.
Pull it out.
One... two...
Again.
Done yet?
It won't. From the back. Again. fast.
That's enough. bitch!
- Damn it!
- Stop.
I got it. go!
Here.
What the hell is this?
First. drag that chest here. fast.
- What?
- Shit.
Hurry. drag the chest. hurry. bitch!
It's gonna eat his whole arm. come on.
Is it gonna be okay?
Hold the head. lay it down.
- Hold the head?
- Lay it down.
Chop it. chop.
Not his head. I mean the shaman's head.
You idiot.
One... two...
Doing what? Doing what?
My finger.
Let's go. let's go.
My finger!
Damn. you said it was safe. bitch!
Now. go back to the
temple for Aod to treat it.
Bonus. please give me some kind of clue.
So I can help avenge you. Amen!
Damn it. my arm is almost off.
And you're just praying to ghosts.
So fake!
I'll fix it. no need for Aod.
- Come.
- Be careful.
Watch out. gently. watch out.
I'll bend it. bitch!
Like this?
Are you cursing me. bitch?
Come here. me. it's me.
Whoa. right in the eyes!
What should we do?
This way.
You. here. did you hear that?
- What now?
- This way.
A gecko! Gecko! Bonus is here.
That's her voice. believe me.
Quick. an important clue. bitch. fast.
- This way!
- Even dead. you're a gecko. bitch.
This door is creepy.
Damn shaman. what's with all this junk?
What? What?
Even kept a wicker tray.
Damn. you scared me.
What?
Your face is bigger than the tray.
Are you mad?
You ass.
Bonus. come out. come out now.
Come out. Bonus. come out
fast. I want to leave.
Stop talking. that's enough.
Why call her. bitch?
Bonus!
What?
Since you're dead. be useful.
Just give a sign.
A sign?
Don't tell me... a sign?
Oh.
This way.
Bitch. you died and became a gecko! Slut!
This fucking way!
A clue!
Bonus dear!
Damn.
Easy. girl. don't get too close to mama.
Hey... you. move it.
Everyone help.
three of us will finish fast. bitch.
I'm this small. how can I lift it?
You're bigger than the cabinet.
you can move it alone.
My hand hurts.
- Stop arguing.
- What's the plan. First?
Together!
- Fast. one-two-three!
- Go.
Heavy. so heavy.
Yeah. so heavy. my arm hurts.
- More than that...
- Damn it.
Come here.
Is it here?
Hey.
- "The dragon is gone..."
- Huh?
That's enough.
You're silly. Move. I'll do it.
"This Makara was bound.
If it is ever summoned.
The soul would enter the statue.
If the statue broke.
The Makara's soul would go below.
Where the Naga once bound it."
Oh. right.
This way.
Hey. hey. you. you.
- Carving?
- Right here.
Is it gonna break like this?
I think it's a clue.
Yim.
Do it.
Me?
Yeah.
I'm on it.
Okay. everyone ready?
Do it right.
Here we go.
Exciting.
You guys. it's going. going!
- Careful.
- Hey.
Oh?
Damn it! Yim!
- How did you light it?
- Move. I'll do it.
- Peary. Peary.
- Stay here.
- Careful.
Get out fast. get out. hurry.
- Out. get out fast.
- Come here.
- Come out now.
- Get out.
Peary! Peary!
Peary.
- Peary.
- Careful.
- Are you okay. brother?
Slowly.
Nothing happened at all.
Stay calm.
- Go. go.
- Carry him. Come.
Go now. go.
Fast. fast. go. go. go.
- Go. don't just stand there. Go.
- Novice. go.
Careful. careful.
Wait for me.
I think it's some kind of carving.
But it's not clear.
Does anyone have some powder?
I don't.
What for?
Here. take this. Mr. Toh.
Here.
Thank you.
Now you're acting pretty.
Cause she's not pretty.
Bitch.
Mine.
What powder is this? Unusual smell.
Well... it's not powder.
It's Bonus' ashes.
What?
Never mind. she'd let us. She's fun.
Use it. She's happy. she's surely happy.
What kind of powder?
I don't know. They said Bonus' ashes.
Uh. I think...
The way to break the statue
Should be about... the moon symbol.
Is it the timing?
A full moon should mean the 15th night.
That's tonight. brother.
As for this water drop symbol.
It's like... the statue
must be hit by some liquid first.
Maybe holy water.
Saliva...
Or could it be Naga tears?
I don't think it's water.
Blood... must be washed with blood.
It's true.
The Naga used blood to bind the Makara.
So we must use Naga blood to break it.
Now you're doomed.
You're the doomed one. Look at yourself.
In this shape. frankly.
you're a dead weight.
- But...
- But what else. bitch?
We'll handle it. Go heal yourself.
Fine.
Where will we find Naga blood?
7-Eleven. maybe?
So stupid. Over there.
Walk faster.
If we fail. we'll have to keep running
from Pee Nak for a month.
Aod. I don't even know
if we'll last that long.
Ugh. this bitch.
Let's get started.
It's ready.
Good job.
Alright.
Here.
What?
I don't dare.
First. please help.
Go on. First. You're the oldest here.
I don't want to take it.
Do it.
Ow. ow. here it comes. ow.
Ow.
Is it done. brother?
I'm scared.
Damn it.
You do it then.
Balloon. come.
Why didn't you say so? Look!
Yes.
My hand isn't great.
- Ooh!
- Yikes!
What are you praying?
I'm concentrating.
Concentrating.
Here goes.
Yes. yes.
- Cut it.
- Yes.
Whoa! I'm scared.
Whoa.
Gosh. this is too sharp.
Then what did you bring it for?
- Prayed until it's sharp.
- Come!
Ready?
Ready.
I'm the one who's ready.
Damn. do it.
- You take it.
- No. First.
- First. don't play around.
- No. you do it.
No. no. you cut it yourself. No.
It might cut my face. No.
Enough. Taking so long. Here!
- That's it.
- Shit.
Done now?
Bitch. a real man.
So mean.
You never come to see me. Bonus.
At least come into my dreams.
that'd be nice.
I miss you. Bonus.
Brother Peary.
Novice. what's wrong?
Why is it just a bit broken?
I think it's not enough blood.
Yim. that's enough!
Yim! Yim!
Stop. Yim!
Hey!
Hey. Yim!
It hurts!
Mr.Toh. come down. Everyone. let's go.
Huh?
Hey!
Mr.Toh!
Mr.Toh.
If he loses more blood. he's gonna die.
If we don't get Naga blood.
we're all dead with him.
What do we do?
The Naga is just like us.
If the heart still clings.
holds on. and craves.
It's like a Naga bound by a Makara.
Never free from suffering and letting go.
If you let go. you are the Naga.
Everyone. buy me some time.
We can. but what are you gonna fight with?
Use my blood. I can take it.
Sure. if it's enough.
- Yim! Yim!
- Yim!
So. who will go first?
It's you. moron!
(Praying)
Let's do this!
Hey!
(Praying)
Mr.Toh
Yim!
Yim
Mr.Toh
Are you okay?
Made it in time?
Mr.Toh
Nin.
Stop. please.
You love them so much. don't you?
Yes.
They're my friends. my brothers.
But you don't love me.
No one loves me.
My booze?
I didn't buy it.
If I did. my brother would starve.
Such a good brother.
Love your brother.
What about me?
Dad. don't hit Nin.
Nott. stay back.
Move!
Nott.
Go sit over there.
You little shit!
Testing me? What's wrong with you?
Why?
Just like your mom?
Only love others. never care about me!
You bastard!
Come here!
How's that?
Always praying.
Feeding all those monks.
What about your dad?
Is your dad just rotting here?
Look at me.
Look!
Look at my face!
Think you're so cool?
I said look at me!
Look!
I'm your fucking father!
You prick!
I'm done. We're over. psycho!
What the hell are you doing?
Stay back.
You stole my girl. you die!
Stay away from what's mine.
Mine! Mine! Mine!
Want to break up with me?
Bitch!
I'm a monk. I can carry it. It's fine.
When I was a novice. you carried mine.
Let me.
A monk can give orders.
Oh. oh. then...
- I'll help.
- Yes.
Help blow the candle.
Sure.
Happy Birthday to you...
Is that so funny?
Uh...
Stay composed.
Yes. Luang Pee.
Happy Birth...
Stay composed.
Don't laugh.
Why poop right now?
Get down. slowly.
Come see me when you're done.
Yes. sir.
Let me kiss your cheeks.
I'm bad because I only saw hate.
Even you. Nott. You hate me too.
I never hated you.
That's not true.
You hate me.
You betrayed me until I died like this.
I never hated you.
Liar!
Nott!
Nak!
Nin. I'm the one who told the police.
If you're angry. be angry at me.
Not brother Nott.
Novice.
Novice. run!
Nott!
Novice.
You...
Why?
Even though I'm so vile.
Because you...
are my brother.
Finally...
I can protect you.
But I can't protect you from your karma.
From what you've done.
You have to face it yourself.
I'll never forget you.
Thank you...
My brother.
I love you.
I love you too.
(Praying)
Nott
How are you? Are you okay?
Does it hurt?
Nott. stay away from that killer.
Nott
Are you okay. Nott?
I... Are you alright. Nott?
Stay away!
Forget it. Sorry. It's over. right?
Nott. you okay?
My whole body pains.
You're so greedy. Yim.
Knowing it was Novice. but telling no one.
I'm sorry. guys.
Sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
I was just worried about him.
Think about it. If I told the truth.
Who knows what would happen to him. right?
May my accumulated merit
protect Nott and his friends
keeping them safe and sound
from the wrath of Pee Nak's spirit.
That I'm the cause of all this vengeance.
Yim. hear something?
Oh. nothing. I just...
heard you wishing for our safety.
That's all.
Don't you smile at me. Novice.
Anyway. Novice...
Sadhu! I'm making a merit.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Go.
Why didn't you tell Nin
that you didn't call the police?
Even if I did. he wouldn't believe me.
He only thought nobody loved him.
The truth that could stop him
was making him see his own wrongs.
Peary. aren't you gonna
help with the monk hood?
True.
I have to go settle something.
Share the merit with Nott for me.
Okay?
Sure. honey.
Go do your mission. We'll follow.
I'm going.
Okay.
Ouch. my life.
Won't make it past the next turn.
Alive?
Dead!
Bonus. let's go home.
Is Bonus this small now?
Don't tie it tight. She can't breathe.
Can you breathe. Bonus?
Isn't she dead?
- I'm going.
- Yeah.
Bye-bye then.
See ya. Peary.
Bye-bye. "Koat Kaprao"
Get out.
Come on. let's take a photo.
Take it for us.
Sure thing.
Right in the middle.
- With the sign?
- With the sign.
- Nice. Very nice.
- Come on.
Laugh for no reason.
Laughing.
- Natural! Natural!
- Natural!
Don't count. just click. Keep clicking.
Came out great.
Hey!
Beautiful.
Novice. don't be funny!
Novice. let me see.
Okay.
No matter how far you are.
Thai Life Insurance will find you.
Thai Life. Thai Life. Thai Life Insurance.
- Kiddee! I knew it!
- Yes.
How did you know we were here?
I called him myself.
For Nott's monk hood?
Yes. but I have something more important.
More important than that?
You know that life is full of uncertainty.
So I want you all to build some security.
As a guarantee for the ones you love.
Build security?
Who else do I love?
- It's just you left. Yim.
- Me?
You called him. why confused?
- Hello.
Here it is. Mr. Yim.
As we discussed.
I've prepared all the papers for you.
Thank you so much.
Just sign here and we're all set.
Sure.
Here you go.
Thanks.
- Okay. thank you very much.
- Thanks.
Now I can rest easy.
Totally easy.
Sign it and you can die now.
Yeah. Yim. just die.
So we can get the money.
Hey. I've only been in a few sequels.
Thank you.
Thank you as well.
It'd be nice if you stayed
here for the Lent.
Thamma Naganimit is like a home for you.
Remember. First?
When we first came. the chapel was scary.
It had that ruined vibe. right?
Renovated and stunning
Seeing this. do you want to ordain again?
Mr.Toh. take a break.
Go ahead. ordain. I won't.
This temple has too many rules.
Hey!
"Just a few."
I'm sorry.
Let's head inside.
Let's go.
Leaving something sacreds.
Don't you regret it?
This amulet has saved us many times.
This Naga amulet has been through so much.
Many eras. many ages. many lives.
But this time. it helped until it broke.
It must be time...
for it to rest.
So the legend of Pee Nak finally ends.
We've all been through it.
All of us? At the worst.
Go back to work. alright Mr.Toh?
Yes.
Everything happened. and not by chance.
Everyone we met.
Every event that occurred.
The pain we passed.
The joy we passed.
They all happened for a reason.
And they've shaped our lives
for days to come.
Our duty...
is to learn and grow from them.
Cravings lead to karma.
Karma leads to consequences.
In the end. if we don't let go.
Our lives will never find true peace.
Sadhu.
What?
Yim!
Guys!
- Watch out. everyone!
- Look!
Luang Pee. help us!
Are you really not gonna
end this. Director Mike?
No! Stay there!
The legend of Pee Nak isn't over.
Mirror.
So what do I change?
I feel sorry for him. like...
Yeah. a bit more. Okay. that works.
Yeah. feel it. Like a brother.
Okay. okay. Good. very good.
I have to take Bonus home.
And settle something first.
Share the meri... merit with...
Take!
Your neck hurts. right?
Pretending to hurt? Wrong.
Share the me... merit with Nott.
Take!
Anu what?
What "anu"?
Anusawari?
Anumodhana...
Leaving something "splashed".
Don't you regret?
Take!
- Sacred!
- Splashed.
If it's splashed. go dry it.
Should we enter the chapel?
Let's look inside.
You first. Novice.
It's alright. go ahead.
You can't walk?
- I can't.
- Then how are you walking?
No walking.
Ow! I can't take it anymore!
- Four ghosts. we still can...
- Cut!
The lights flickered. I knew it. Scared me.
You are bit too loud.
And where will we get Naga blood?
There.
So... stupid.
- Cut!
- Cut.
This one guy. when
he's stuck. he just nods.
So stupid!
Yes. if it's enough.
- Not letting me speak?
- Not yet?
Didn't let me say a word.
- Let me play too.
- Calm down.
Concentrate. concentrate.
Shit. it didn't.
Damn. wrong side.
First. what did you bring?
Cut. cut. cut. cut.
Aim James wants to play.
Aim James. you're ruining the mood.
You bastard!
You hit my brother. bitch.
I give up.
Shit!
What?
Always me. dammit.
Where are my glasses?
Look. they're broken.
I'll buy you new ones.
You okay?
I wanted to play too. I'm lost.
Dammit. every single time.
(Praying)
Sadhu! Sadhu!
You think fucking a Nak
right before his ordination...
can be cleansed with a monk's robe?
I'll be your hell.
haunting your every step.
A lustful soul like you
can never be a monk.